worshiphousemedia.com 2007-12-14

# Worship House Media, the one-stop-shop for your church media and video ministry

At WorshipHouse Media, we strive to develop an innovative online experience to better serve our users. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our online store with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. 

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.

**Data collection**

• Some areas of worshiphousemedia.com do not require any personally identifying information.  
• WorshipHouse Media collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.  
• Some of the features of worshiphousemedia.com require you to register for an account. WorshipHouse Media asks you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, shipping address, billing adddress, email address and a password for your account) and we will use that information to provide the service.  
• When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.

**Cookies**

• Upon your first visit to WorshipHouse Media, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some WorshipHouse Media features or services may not function properly without cookies.

**Information sharing**

• We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:  
\- We have your consent.  
\- If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.  
\- In the event of a transfer of ownership of WorshipHouse Media, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  

**Information security**

• We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.  
• We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

**Updating your information**

• We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information in the my account section of our site.

**Changes to this Policy**

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time.
